Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Happy Song  (4:21)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
We are down,
we are crazy fools everyday at school.
Teachers here, teachers there,
Books and books,
they are everywhere.
Come on boys, we need to dance,
we have got a good chance.
Lay your problems on the floor,
clap your hands and sing once more:
Everybody, let's go to the king
We can dance there,
dance and eat an ice-cream.
Everybody dancing all night long,
Try to do it, sing a happy song.
Music, dancing in the night,
we can get so high,
For no reason no long stop,
now's the time to go to the top.
It's a sweeter happy song,
we'll sing all night long.
Lay your problems on the floor,
clap your hands and sing once more:
Everybody, let's go to the king,...
We can dance there, dance and eat an ice-cream
Every-body dancing all night long
Try to do it sing a happy song
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Happy Song  (4:21)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Happy song
Let's go, let's go boys,
come with me and sing, sing a happy song.
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Happy Song  (4:21)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
Come on boys, we need to dance,
we all have got a good, good chance.
Lay your problems on the floor,
clap your hands and sing once more.
Music sound in the night,
we all can get so high,
For no reason no long stop,
now's the time to go to the top.
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Happy Song  (4:21)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
We are down,
we are crazy fools everyday at school. ...
Teachers here, teachers there
Books and books
they are everywhere
Come on boys, we need to dance,
we have got a good chance. ...
Lay your problems on the floor
Clap your hands and sing once more
Everybody, let's go to the king. ...
We can dance there, dance and eat an ice-cream
Everybody dancing all night long
Trying to do it sing a happy song
Happy song
Let's go, let's go boys,
come with me and sing, sing a happy song.
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Happy Song  (4:21)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
Everybody, let's go to the king. ...
We can dance there, dance and eat an ice-cream
Everybody dancing all night long
Trying to do it sing a happy song
Everybody, let's go to the king,...
We can dance there
Dance and eat an ice-cream
Every body dancing all night long
Trying to do it
sing a happy song
everybody -