Freeze! I'm Ma baker - put your hands in the air,
Gimme all your money
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Ma Baker (4:58)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
She was the meanest cat
In old chicago town
She really moved them down
She had no heart at all
No no no heart at all
She was the meanest cat
Oh she was really tough
She left her husband flat
He wasn't tough enough
She took her boys along
'cos they were mean and strong
Ma ma ma ma - ma baker
She taught her four sons
To handle their guns
Ma ma ma ma - ma baker
She never could cry
But she knew how to die
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Ma Baker (4:58)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
Here is a special bulletin.
Ma baker is the FBI's most wanted woman.
Her photo is hanging on every post office wall.
If you have any information about this woman,
Please contact the nearest police station...
put your hands in the air
Don't anybody move!
They left a trail of crime
Across the U.S.A
And when one boy was killed
She realy made them pay
She had no heart at all
No no no heart at all
Ma ma ma ma - ma baker
She taught her four sons
To handle their guns
Ma ma ma ma - ma baker
She never could cry
But she knew how to die
put your hands in the air
Freeze!
Don't anybody move!
One day they robbed a bank
It was their last hooray
The cops appeared too soon
They could't get away
And all the loot they had
It made them mighty mad
And so they shot it out
Ma Baker and her sons
They didn't waant to hang
They died with blazing guns
And so the story ends
Of one who left no friends
Ma ma ma ma - ma baker
She taught her four sons
To handle their guns
Ma ma ma ma - ma baker
She never could cry
But she knew how to die