Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Boney M - Hooray Hooray it's a holi - hiliday (3:12)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Diggy di di doo diggy diggy di doo (hi dee hi dee ho)
Diggy di di doo diggy diggy di di (hi dee hi dee ho)
Theres place I know where we should go (hi dee hi dee ho)
Wont you take me there, your lady fair (hi dee hi dee ho)
Theres a brook nearby, the grass grows high (hi dee hi dee ho)
Where we both can hide side by side (hi dee hi dee ho)
Hooray, hooray, its a holi-holiday
What a world of fun for everyone, holi-holiday
Sing a summer song, skip along, holi-holiday
Its a holi-holiday
Theres a country fair not far from there (hi dee hi dee ho)
On a carousels the ding-dong bell (hi dee hi dee ho)
On the loop-di-loop well swing and swoop (hi dee hi dee ho)
And what else well do is up to you (hi dee hi dee ho)
Hooray, hooray, its a holi-holiday
What a world of fun for everyone, holi-holiday
Sing a summer song, skip along, holi-holiday
Its a holi-holiday
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Boney M - Hooray Hooray it's a holi - hiliday (3:12)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Well, Im game, fun is the thing Im after
Now lets all live it up today, get set for love and laughter
Well, lets go, time isnt here for wasting
Life is so full of sweet sweet things, Id like to do some tasting
Hooray, hooray, its a holi-holiday
What a world of fun for everyone, holi-holiday
Sing a summer song, skip along, holi-holiday
Its a holi-holiday
Hooray, hooray, its a holi-holiday
What a world of fun for everyone, holi-holiday
Its a holi-holiday