Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: No Woman No Cry (3:38)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
No woman no cry
Cause i remember when we used to sit
In a government yard in trenchtown
Observing the hypocrites
Mingle with the good people we meet
Good friends we have, now
Good friends we have lost
Along the way
In this great future,
You can't forget your past
So dry your tears, i say
No woman no cry
Oh little darling, don't shed no tears
Cause i remember when we used to sit
In the government yard in trenchtown
When georgie would make the fire lights
I say, log would burnin' through the nights
Then we would cook cornmeal porridge
Of which I’ll share with you
My feet is my only carriage
So I’ve got to push on thru,
And while I’m gone
Everything 's gonna be alright
Everything 's gonna be alright now
No woman no cry
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: No Woman No Cry (3:38)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
No woman no cry
Oh little darlin' don't shed no tears
Said i re, said i re, said i remember
No woman no cry