Mary's boy child Jesus Christ,
was born on Christmas Day.
And man will live for evermore,
because of Christmas Day.
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Mary's Boy Child Oh My Lord (5:09)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Long time ago in Bethlehem,
so the Holy Bible said,
Mary's boy child Jesus Christ,
was born on Christmas Day.
Hark, now hear the angels sing,
a king was born today,
And man will live for evermore,
because of Christmas Day.
Mary's boy child Jesus Christ,
was born on Christmas Day.
While shepherds watch their flocks by night,
they see a bright new shining star,
they hear a choir sing a song,
the music seemed to come from afar.
Hark, now hear the angels sing,
a king was born today,
And man will live for evermore,
because of Christmas Day.
Artist: Boney M
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Mary's Boy Child Oh My Lord (5:09)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-03-31
For a moment the world was aglow,
all the bells rang out
there were tears of joy and laughter,
people shouted "let everyone know,
there is hope for all to find peace".
And then they found a little nook
in a stable all forlorn,
and in a manger cold and dark,
Mary's little boy was born.
Hark, now hear the angels sing,
a king was born today,
And man will live for evermore,
because of Christmas Day.
Mary's boy child Jesus Christ,
was born on Christmas Day.
Oh a moment still worth was a glow,
all the bells rang out
there were tears of joy and laughter,
people shouted "let everyone know,
there is hope for all to find peace".
Oh my Lord
You sent your son to save us
Your very self you gave us
Oh my Lord
That sin may not enslave us
And love may reign once more
Oh my Lord
when in the crib they found him
A golden halo crowned him
Oh my Lord
They gathered all around him
To see him and adore
(This day will live forever)
Oh my Lord (So praise the Lord)
They had become to doubt you
Oh my Lord (He is the truth forever)
What did they know about you
Oh my Lord (So praise the Lord)
But they were lost without you
They needed you so bad (His light is shining on us)
Oh my Lord (So praise the Lord)
with the child's adoration
Oh my lord (He is a personation)
There came great jubilation
Oh my Lord (So praise the Lord)
And full of admiration
They realized what they had (until the sun falls from the sky)
Oh my Lord (Oh praise the Lord)
You sent your son to save us
Oh my Lord (This day will live forever)
Your very self you gave us
Oh my Lord (So praise the Lord)
That sin may not enslave us
And love may reign once more