Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: All that I need (3:41)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-01
I was lost and alone
Trying to grow,
making my way down that long winding road
Had no reason, no rhyme
Like a song out of time
And there you were, standing in front of my eyes
How could I be such a fool
To let go of love and break all the rules
Girl when you walked out that door
left a hole in my heart
And now I know for sure
You're the air that I breathe
Girl you're all that I need
And I wanna thank you, lady
You're the words that I read
You're the light that I see
And your love is all that I need
Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: All that I need (3:41)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-01
I was searching in vain
Playing a game
Had no-one else but myself left to blame
You came into my world
No diamonds or pearls
Could ever replace what you gave to me girl
Just like a castle of sand
Girl, I almost let love slip right out of my hands
And just like a flower needs rain
I will stand by your side through the joy and the pain
You're the air that I breathe
Girl you're all that I need
And I wanna thank you, lady
You're the words that I read
You're the light that I see
And your love is all that I need
Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: All that I need (3:41)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-01
You're the air that I breathe
Girl you're all that I need
And I wanna thank you, lady
You're the words that I read
You're the light that I see
And your love is all that I need
You're the song that I say
You're my everything
And I wanna thank you, lady
You're all that I need, girl
You're the air that I breathe, yeah
And I want to thank you
You're the words that I read, girl
You're love is all I need, yeah
And I want to thank you
(and I want to thank you, lady)
You're all that I need, girl
You're the air that I breathe, yeah
And I want to thank you..