Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Words (4:01)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-02
Smile, an everlasting smile
A smile can bring you near to me
Don't ever let me find you wrong
Cause that would bring a tear to me
This world has lost it's glory
Lets start a brand new story
Now my love
You think that I don't even mean
A single word I say...
It's only words
And words are all I have
To take your heart away
Talk, in everlasting words
And dedicate them all, to me
And I will give you all my life
I'm here if you should call to me
You think that I don't even mean
a single word I say...
It's only words
And words are all I have
To take your heart away
It's only words
And words are all I have
To take your heart away
Da da da da da da da
Da da da da da da da da
This world has lost it's glory
Let's start a brand new story
Now, my love
You think that I don't even mean
a single word I say...
It's only words
And words are all I have
To take your heart away
It's only words
And words are all I have
To take your heart away
It's only words
And words are all I have
To take your heart away