Chica cha ha ha
No matter what they tell us
No matter what they do
No matter what they teach us
What we believe it's true
No matter what they call us
However they attack
No matter where they take us
We'll find our own way back
I can't deny what I believe
I can't be what I'm not
I know our love forever
I know no matter what
If only tears were laughter(ooh)
If only night was day(ooh)
If only prayers were answered
(hear my prayers)
Then we could hear God say(say)
No matter what they tell you
No matter what they do
No matter what they teach you
What you believe it's true
And I will keep you safe and strong
And shelter from the storm
No matter where it's barren
A dream is being born
Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: No Matter What (4:33)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-01
No matter who they follow
No matter where they leave
No matter how they judge us
I'll be everyone you need
No matter if the sun don't shine
( the sun don't shine)
Or if the skies are blue
(skies are blue)
No matter what the end is
My life began with you
I can't deny what I believe
( what I believe)
I can't be what I'm not
(I know I know )
I know this love's forever
That's all that matters now
No matter what
NO no matter what
No,no matter what
That's all that matters to me