Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Love Me For A Reason (3:35)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-01
Girl when you hold me
How you control me
You bend and you fold me
Any way you please
It must be easy for you
To love the things that you do
But just a pastime for you
I could never be
And I never know, girl
If I should stay or go
Cos the games that you play
Are driving me away...
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl
Love me for a reason
Let the reason be love
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl
Love me for a reason
Let the reason be love
Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Love Me For A Reason (3:35)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-01
Kisses and caresses
Are only minor tests, babe
Of love turned to stresses
Between a woman and a man
So if love everlasting
Isn't what you're asking
I'll have to pass, girl
I'm proud to take a stand
I can't continue guessing
Because it's only messing
With my pride, and my mind
So write down this time to time
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl
Love me for a reason
Let the reason be love
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl
Love me for a reason
Let the reason be love
Artist: Boyzone
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Love Me For A Reason (3:35)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-01
I'm just a little old-fashioned
It takes more than a physical attraction
My initial reaction is
Honey give me a love
Not a fascimile of
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl
Love me for a reason
Let the reason be love
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl
Love me for a reason
Let the reason be love
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl
Love me for a reason
Let the reason be love
Don't love me for fun, girl
Let me be the one, girl