Artist: Brian Adams
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Everything I Do I Do It For You (6:42)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Look into my eyes - you will see
What you mean to me
Search your heart - search your soul
And when you find me
there you'll search no more
Don't tell me it's not worth tryin' for
You can't tell me it's not worth dyin' for
You know it's true
Everything I do - I do it for you
Look into my heart - you will find
There's nothin' there to hide
Take me as I am - take my life
I would give it all I would sacrifice
Don't tell me it's not worth fightin' for
I can't help it
there's nothin' I want more
You know it's true
Everything I do - I do it for you
There's no love - like your love
And no other - could give more love
There's nowhere - unless you're there
All the time - all the way
Artist: Brian Adams
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Everything I Do I Do It For You (6:42)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Oh you can't tell me
it's not worth tryin' for.
I can't help it
there's nothin' I want more
I would fight for you - I'd lie for you
Walk the wire for you - Ya I'd die for you
Ya know it's true
Everything I do - I do it for you
Artist: Brian Adams
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Every thing i do i do it for you (6:42)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03