Artist: Brian Adams
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Please For Give Me (5:53)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Still feels like our first night together
Feels like the first kiss..
And it's gettin better baby
No one can better this
Still holdin on.. you're still the one
The first time our eyes met
The same feeling I get..
Only feels much stronger
I wanna love you longer
You still turn the fire on..
So if you're feelin lonely don't
You're the only one I'll ever want
I only wanna make it good
So if I love ya a little more than I should..
Please forgive me, I know not what I do
Please forgive me, I can't stop lovin you
Don't deny me, this pain I'm goin through
Please forgive me, if need you like I do
Please believe me, every word I say is true..
Please forgive me, I can't stop lovin you..
Artist: Brian Adams
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Please For Give Me (5:53)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Still feels like our best times are together
Feels like the first touch..
We're still gettin closer baby..
Can't get close enough
Still holdin on.. still number one
I remember the smell of your skin
I remember everything...
I remember all your moves..
I remember you, yeah..
I remember the nights.. you know i still do
So if you're feelin lonely don't
You're the only one i'll ever want
I only wanna make it good
So if I love ya a little more than I should
Please forgive me, I know not what I do
Please forgive me, I can't stop lovin you
Don't deny me, this pain I'm goin through
Please forgive me, if I need you like I do
Oh, believe me, every word I say is true
Please forgive me, I can't stop lovin you
Artist: Brian Adams
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Please For Give Me (5:53)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
The one thing I'm sure of.. is the way we make love
The one thing I depend on.. is for us to stay strong
With every word and every breath I'm prayin..
That's why I'm sayin..
Please forgive me, I know not what I do
Please forgive me, I can't stop lovin you
Don't deny me, this pain I'm goin through
Please forgive me, if I need you like I do
Babe, believe me, every word I say is true
Please forgive me, if I can't stop lovin you
Oh, believe me, I don't know what I do
Please forgive me, I can't stop lovin you
Can't stop.. lovin you