Artist: Britney Spears
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han, TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Somestimes
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
You tell me you're in love with me
That you can't take your pretty eyes away from me
It's not that I don't want to stay
But everytime you come to close I move away
I wanna believe in everything that you say
Because it sounds so good
But if you really want me, move it slow
There's things about me you just have to know
Sometimes I run Sometimes I hide
sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight
Treat you right, be with you day and night
baby all I need is time
I don't wanna be so shy, uh-uh
Everytime I am alone I wonder why
Hope that you will wait for me
You see that, you're the only one for me
I wanna believe in everything that you say
Cause it sounds so good
but if you really want me, move it slow
There's things about me, you just have to know
Sometimes I run (Sometimes) Sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight
Treat you right, be with you day and night
All I really want is to hold you tight
treat you right, be with you day and night
Baby, all I need is time
Just hang around and you'll see
There's nowhere ill ever be
If you love me, trust in me
The way that I trust in you
Sometimes I run (Sometimes) Sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight (hold ya tight)
Treat you right, be with you day and night (day and night)
Sometimes I run Sometimes I hide (sometimes)
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight treat you right,
be with you day and night (day and night)
All I really want is to hold you tight Treat you right,
be with you day and night
baby, all I need is tim
Sometimes I run (Sometimes) Sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight (hold ya tight)