Artist: Caught In The Act
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Wishing You Were Here (4:47)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
When I think of you it압 just the same
This feeling it could never change
Believe me
It fills me up with joy and happiness
Though there is only emptiness
Around me
In the night
All I do is run
Run away
From all what압 in my head, my heart, my soul
Trying to forget
So I fight a war so lost
I just can앖 win
But something deep inside tells me
Hold on, not to give in
When will you see
You still belong to me
Wishing you were here now
Let your inside outside
Open your heart and love you앏l find
I앐 wishing you were here now
Trying to find a way out
Out of this confusion in my mind
I앐 wishing you were here
What압 in your mind
I wanna know
In the streets a million people pass me by
In every face I see your eyes
Still shining
Ooh, I miss your caring warm embrace
Your tender touch, your kisses taste
Just crying
So I fight a war so lost I cannot win
There압 something deep inside tells me
Hold on, I can앖 give in.
When will you see you still belong to me
Wishing you were here now
Let your inside outside
Open your heart and love you앏l find
I앐 wishing you were here now
Trying to find a way out
Out of this confusion in my mind
Wishing you were here, to hold me
Wishing you were here, to touch me
Wishing you were here with me again
Wishing you were here, to kiss me
Wishing you were here, to hold me
Wishing you were here with me again
you belong to me
When will you see
You still belong to me
Wishing you were here, to hold me
Wishing you were here, to touch me
Wishing you were here with me again
Wishing you were here, to hold me
Wishing you were here, to touch me
Wishing you were here with me again
Wishing you were here, to hold me
Wishing you were here, to touch me
Wishing you were here with me again
I앐 wishing you were here now