The whispers in the morning
Of lovers sleeping tight
Are rolling like thunder now
As I look in your eyes
I hold on to your body
And feel each move you make
Your voice is warm and tender
A love that I could not forsake
'Coz I am your lady
And you are my man
Whenever you reach for me
I'll do all that I can
Lost is how I'm feeling,
lying in your arms.
When the world outside's too much to take
that all ends when I'm with you.
Even though there may be times,
it seems I'm far away,
never wonder where I am,
'cause I am always by your side.
'Coz I am your lady
And you are my man
Whenever you reach for me
I'll do all that I can
We're heading for something
Somewhere I've never been
Sometimes I am frightened
But I'm ready to learn
Of the power of love
The sound of your heart beating made it clear.
Suddenly the feeling that I can't go on
is light years away.
'Coz I am your lady
And you are my man
Whenever you reach for me
I'll do all that I can
We're heading for something
Somewhere I've never been
Sometimes I am frightened
But I'm ready to learn
Of the power of love
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: The Power Of Love (5:40)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Sometimes I am frightened
But I'm ready to learn
Of the power of love
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: The Power Of Love
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03