Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: My Heart Will Go On (4:38)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Every night in my dreams
I see you. I feel you.
That is how I know you go on.
Far across the distance
And spaces between us
You have come to show you go on.
Near, far, wherever you are
I believe that the heart does go on
Once more you open the door
And you're here in my heart
And my heart will go on and on
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: My Heart Will Go On (4:38)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Love can touch us one time
And last for a lifetime
And never go 'til we're one
Love was when I loved you
One true time I hold to
In my life we'll always go on
Near, far, wherever you are
I believe that the heart does go on
(Why does the heart go on)
Once more you open the door
And you're here in my heart
And my heart will go on and on
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: My Heart Will Go On (4:38)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
You're here, there's nothing I fear,
And I know that my heart will go on
We'll stay forever this way
You are safe in my heart
And my heart will go on and on
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: My Heart Will Go On (4:38)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03