Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Let's Talk About Love (5:01)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Every where I go all the places that I've been
Every smile is a new horizon
On a land I've never seen
There are people around the world
Different faces,defferent names
But that's one true emotion
That reminds me we aren't the same
Let's talk about love
From the laughter of a child
To the tears of a grown man
There's a thread
That runs straight through us
And helps us understand
And subtle as a breeze
That fans a flicker to a frame
From the very first sweet melody
To the very last refrain
Let's talk about love, let's talk about us
Let's talk about life, let's talk about trust
Let's talk about love
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Let's Talk About Love (5:01)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
It's the king of all who live
And queen of all good hearts
It's the one you may keep up your sleeve
'Til the name is all out lost
As deep as any sea
with the rage of any storm
But as gentle as a falling leaf
On any autumn morn
Let's talk about love, let's talk about us
Let's talk about life, let's talk about trust
Let's talk about love, it's all we are needing
Let's talk about us, it's the air we're breathing
Let's talk about life, I wanna know you
Let's talk about trust, I wanna show you
Every where I go all the places that I've been
Every smile is a new horizon
On a land I've never seen
There are people around the world
Different faces, defferent names
But that's one true emotion
That reminds me we aren't the same
Let's talk about love, let's talk about us
Let's talk about life, let's talk about trust