Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: The Power Of The Dream (4:27)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Deep within each heart
There lies a magic spark
That lights the fire of our imagination
And since the dawn of man
The strenght of just "I can"
Has brought together people of all nations
There's nothing ordinary
In the living of each day
There's a special part
Every one of us will play
Feel the flame forever burn
Teaching lessons we must learn
To bring us closer to the power of the dream
As the world gives us its best
To stand apart from all the rest
It is the power of the dream that brings us here
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: The Power Of The Dream (4:27)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Your mind will take you far
The rest is just pure heart
You'll find your fate is all your own creation
Every boy and girl
As they come into this world
They bring the gift of hope and inspiration
Feel the flame forever burn
Teaching lessons we must learn
To bring us closer to the power of the dream
The world unites in hope and peace
We pray that it will always be
It is the power of the dream that brings us here
Artist: Celine Dion
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: The Power Of The Dream (4:27)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
There's so much strength in all of us
Every woman child and man
It's the moment that you think you can't
You'll discover that you can
Feel the flame forever burn
Teaching lessons we must learn
To bring us closer to the power of the dream
The world unites in hope and peace
We pray that it will always be
It is the power of the dream that brings us here
Feel the flame forever burn
Teaching lessons we must learn
To bring us closer to the power of the dream
The world unites in hope and peace
We pray that it will always be
It is the power of the dream that brings us here
The power of the dream
The faith in things unseen
The courage to embrace your fear
No matter where you are
To reach for your own star
To realize the power of the dream