Artist: Elton John
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Sacrifice (4:33)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
It's a human sign
When things go wrong
When the scent of her lingers
And temptation's strong
Into the boundary
Of each married man
Sweet deceit comes calling
And negativity lands
Cold cold heart
Hard done by you
Some things look better baby
Just passing through
And it's no sacrifice
Just a simple word
It's two hearts living
In two separate worlds
But it's no sacrifice
No sacrifice
It's no sacrifice at all
Artist: Elton John
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Sacrifice (4:33)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Mutual misunderstanding
After the fact
Sensitivity builds a prison
In the final act
We lose direction
No stone unturned
No tears to damn you
When jealousy burns
Cold cold heart
Hard done by you
Some things look better baby
Just passing through
And it's no sacrifice
Just a simple word
It's two hearts living
In two separate worlds
But it's no sacrifice
No sacrifice
It's no sacrifice at all
Artist: Elton John
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Sacrifice (4:33)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Cold cold heart
Hard done by you
Some things look better baby
Just passing through
And it's no sacrifice
Just a simple word
It's two hearts living
In two separate worlds
But it's no sacrifice
No sacrifice
It's no sacrifice at all