Artist: Elton John
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Can You Feel the Love Tonight (3:58)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
There's a calm surrender
To the rush of day
When the heat of the rolling world
Can be turned away
And enchanted moment
And it sees me through
It's enough for this restless
Just to be with you
And can you feel the love tonight?
It is where we are
It is enough for this wide-eyed wanderer
That we got this far
And can you feel the love tonight?
How it's laid to rest
It's enough to make kings and vagabonds
Believe the very best
Artist: Elton John
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Can You Feel the Love Tonight (3:58)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
There's a time for everyone
If they only learn
That the twisting kaleidoscope
Moves us all in turn
There's a phyme and reason
To the wild outdoors
When the heart of this star-crossed voyager
Beats in time with yours
And can you feel the love tonight?
It is where we are
It is enough for this wide-eyed wanderer
That we got this far
And can you feel the love tonight?
How it's laid to rest
It's enough to make kings and vagabonds
Believe the very best