Artist: Eric Clapton
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Wonderful Tonight (4:53)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
It's late in the evening
she's wondering what close to wear
she puts on her make up
and brushes her long blond her
and than she ask me: "Do I look allright?"
and I say: "yes, you look wonderful tonight"
Artist: Eric Clapton
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Wonderful Tonight (4:53)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
We go to a party
and everyone turns to see
this beautiful lady
is walking around with me
and than she ask me: "do you feel allright?"
and I say: "yes, I feel wonderful tonight"
I feel wonderful because I see the love
lighting in your eyes
and the wonder of it all
is that you just don't realize
how much I love you...
Artist: Eric Clapton
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Wonderful Tonight (4:53)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
It's time to go home now
and I've got make her
so I give her the car keys
and she helps me to bed
and than I tell her
as I turn off the light
I said: "my darling, you are wonderful tonight"
"oh my darling, you are wonderful tonight"