Artist: Eric Clapton
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Change The World (3:55)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
If I could reach the stars
Pull one down for you
Shine it on my heart
So you could see the truth
That this love I have inside
Is everything it seems
But for now I find
It's only in my dreams
If I can change the world
I would be the sunlight in your universe
You would think my love was really something good
Baby if I could change the world
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Change The World (3:55)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
If I could be king
Even for a day
I'd take you as my queen
I'd have no other way
And our love will rule
In this kingdom we have made
'Til then I'll be a fool
Wishing for the day
If I can change the world
I would be the sunlight in your universe
You would think my love was really something good
Baby if I could change the world
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Change The World (3:55)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
If I can change the world
I would be the sunlight in your universe
You would think my love was really something good
Baby if I could change the world