Now and forever
Until the time is through
I can't believe it
I don't know where to start
No baby
So many questions
Deep inside of my heart
Give me a moment before you go
There's something you ought to know
Baby ,now and forever
Until the time is through
I'll be stand here
Waiting and never
Give up my faith in you
Try to make it clear
Without your love
I'll be half a man
Maybe one day
You 'll understand
Now and forever
Until the time through
I'll be waiting
How can I tell you
So that you can see
You know that
Love has a meaning
When you are here with me
Give me a moment before you go
There's something you ought to know
Baby, now and forever
Until the time is through
I'll be stand here
Waiting and never
Give up my faith in you
Try to make it clear
Without your love
I'll be half a man
Maybe one day
You 'll understand
Now and forever
Until the time through
There is no one to comfort me
Here in my cold reality
I'm searching for words
What can I say
To make you see
Baby now
Until the time is through
I'll be here,girl
Baby now
Until the time is through
I'll be here,girl
Baby, now and forever
Until the time is through
I'll be stand here
Waiting and never
Give up my faith in you
Try to make it clear
Without your love
I'll be half a man
Maybe one day
You 'll understand
Now and forever
I'll be here for you
Until the time is through