(yeah, like that)
(you know what I mean)
(you’re looking kinda fly tonight girl)
(what’s up)
(check it)
Baby when the lights go out
I’ll show you what it’s all about
(coming at you girl, you know you like this girl)
(here we go) (check it)
I ain’t sorry for the way I feel
I know you think I’m being insincere
From the way I’m treating you
The only one thing on my mind
Is just kicking it with you girl
Baby it’s not the way I feel,
you know you must believe me
Baby it’s not part of the deal (oh no no)
Baby when the lights go out
Every single word can not express,
the love and tenderness
I’ll show you what it’s all about
Babe I swear you will succumb to me,
so baby come to me
When the lights go out
(yeah, check it) (check it out, second verse girl)
I know you think it may be just a lie
Ain’t no use in putting up a fight
Cos my heart is set on you
I see the truth, it’s in your eyes
I ain’t fooled by your thin disguise
I can see I’m getting through babe
Girl don’t deny the way you feel,
you know you’ve gotta trust me
Give me a chance to prove I’m real (oh yeah yeah)
I never wanted to be so unkind
Baby when the lights go out
Every single word can not express,
the love and tenderness
I’ll show you what it’s all about
Babe I swear you will succumb to me,
so baby come to me
When the lights go out
Every single word can not express,
the love and tenderness
I’ll show you what it’s all about
Babe I swear you will succumb to me,
so baby come to me
When the lights go out
Artist: Five
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han, TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: When The Light Go Out (4:09)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Baby when the lights go out
Every single word can not express,
the love and tenderness
I’ll show you what it’s all about
Babe I swear you will succumb to me,
so baby come to me
When the lights go out
Baby when the lights go out
Every single word can not express,
the love and tenderness
I’ll show you what it’s all about
Babe I swear you will succumb to me,
so baby come to me
When the lights go out