Artist: Michael Jackson
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Earth Song (6:45)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-08
What about sunrise
What about rain
What about all the things
That you said we were to gain.. .
What about killing fields
Is there a time
What about all the things
That you said was yours and mine...
Did you ever stop to notice
All the blood we've shed before
The crying Earth the weeping shores?
Aaaaaaaaaah Aaaaaaaaaah
What have we done to the world
Look what we've done
What about all the peace
That you pledge your only son...
What about flowering fields
Is there a time
What about all the dreams
That you said was yours and mine...
Did you ever stop to notice
All the children dead from war
The crying Earth the weeping shores
Artist: Michael Jackson
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Earth Song (6:45)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-08
I used to dream
I used to glance beyond the stars
Now I don't know where we are
Although I know we've drifted far
Aaaaaaaaaah Aaaaaaaaaah
Artist: Michael Jackson
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Earth Song (6:45)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-08
Hey, what about yesterday, what about us
What about the seas, what about us
The heavens are falling down, what about us
I can't even breathe, what about us
What about the bleeding Earth, what about us
Can't we feel its wounds, what about us
What about nature's worth, ooo,ooo
It's our planet's womb, what about us
What about animals, what about it
We've turned kingdoms to dust, what about us
What about elephants, what about us
Have we lost their trust, what about us
What about crying whales, what about us
We're ravaging the seas, what about us
What about forest trails, ooo, ooo
Burnt despite our pleas, what about us
What about the holy land, what about it
Torn apart by creed, what about us
What about the common man, what about us
Can't we set him free, what about us
What about children dying, what about us
Can't you hear them cry, what about us
Where did we go wrong, ooo, ooo
Someone tell me why, what about us
What about babies, what about it
What about the days, what about us
What about all their joy, what about us
What about the man, what about us
What about the crying man, what about us
What about Abraham, what was us
What about death again, ooo, ooo
Do we give a damn
Aaaaaaaaaah Aaaaaaaaaah
Artist: Michael Jackson
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Earth Song (6:45)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-08