Artist: Michael Jackson
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: You Are Not Alone (5:44)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-11
Another day has gone
I'm still all alone
How could this be
You're not here with me
You never said goodbye
Someone tell me why
Did you have to go
And leave my world so cold
Everyday I sit and ask myself
How did love slip away
Something whispers in my ear and says
That you are not alone
For I am here with you
Though you're far away
I am here to stay
You are not alone
I am here with you
Though we're far apart
You're always in my heart
You are not alone
All alone
Why, oh
Just the other night
I thought I heard you cry
Asking me to come
And hold you in my arms
I can hear your prayers
Your burdens I will bear
But first I need your hand
So forever can begin
Everyday I sit and ask myself
How did love slip away
Then something whispers in my ear and says
That you are not alone
For I am here with you
Though you're far away
I am here to stay
For you are not alone
I am here with you
Though we're far apart
You're always in my heart
And you are not alone
Oh...
Whisper three words and I'll come runnin'
Fly...
And girl you know that I'll be there
I'll be there
You are not alone
I am here with you
Though you're far away
I am here to stay
You are not alone
I am here with you
Though we're far apart
You're always in my heart
You are not alone(You are not alone)
For I am here with you(I am here with you)
Though you're far away(Though you're far away)
I am here to stay(And you with me)
For you are not alone(You're always)
In my heart.....For I am here with you
Heart.....Though we're far apart
Heart.....You're always in my heart
For you are not alone
Not alone
You are not alone, you are not alone...
Not alone, not alone
You just reach for me girl
In the morning in the evening
Not alone, not alone
And you with me, not alone
Oh, together, together...