Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Atlantis Is Calling (S.O.S For Love) (3:51)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Lady, I know it was hard
But it's much harder to ignore
There's a chance and I'll promise
I won't hurt you anymore
Hollywood nights we're romancin'
You can trust me anytime
Somewhere, oh babe, there's someone
Oh you're dancing in my mind
Ohoho, little queenie
I'm your fool
Come on, teach me the rules
I will send a S.O.S. for love
Ohoho, little queenie,
I'm your fool
You need love, like I do
I will send a S.O.S. for love
Atlantis is calling, S.O.S. for love
Atlantis is calling, from the stars above
Atlantis is calling, it's too hot to stop
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Atlantis Is Calling (S.O.S For Love) (3:51)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
If loving you is wrong, babe
Oh, I don't wanna be right
I've got you under my skin, babe
And baby, hold me tight
I'm ready for our romance
I wait a million years for you
I love you more than I'm saying
Baby, that's for me the truth
Ohoho, little queenie
I'm your fool
Come on, teach me the rules
I will send a S.O.S. for love
Ohoho, little queenie,
I'm your fool
You need love, like I do
I will send a S.O.S. for love
Atlantis is calling, S.O.S. for love
Atlantis is calling, from the stars above
Atlantis is calling, it's too hot to stop
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Atlantis Is Calling (S.O.S For Love) (3:51)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Atlantis is calling, S.O.S. for love
Atlantis is calling, from the stars above
Atlantis is calling, it's too hot to stop
Atlantis is calling, S.O.S. for love
Atlantis is calling, from the stars above