Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Doctor For My Heart (3:21)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Babe how can you mend a broken heart
Oh you're tearin' me apart
Thousand drums play in my mind
Take it off him put it on me
Oh I'm feelin' so lonely
And I'm holdin' back my spleen
I don't wanna a doctor, for my heart
Oh I wanna, try a brand-new start
I don't wanna, a doctor for my heart
Oh I wanna, commander of my love
I don't wanna, a doctor for my Lonely heartache
My heart believes your love beat lady
Come take a chance on love
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Doctor For My Heart (3:21)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
I can't give you anything but love
Take these chains from your heart
Thousand drums play in my mind
Babe however hard I try bluer I get
Don't put my love in a dirty bag
Until it ends there is no end
I don't wanna, a doctor for my heart
Oh I wanna, try a brand-new start
I don't wanna, commander of my love
I don't wanna a doctor for my lonely heartache
My heart believes your love beat lady
Come take a chance on love
I don't wanna a doctor for my heart
Oh I wanna try a brand-new start
Oh I wanna , a doctor for my heart
I don't wanna, commander of my love