Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: You Can Win If You Want (3:50)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
You packed your things in a carpetbag
Left home - never looking back
Rings on your fingers, paint on your toes
Music wherever you go
You don't fit in a smalltown world
But I feel you're the girl for me
Rings on your fingers, paint on your toes
You're leaving town where nobody knows
You can win if you want
If you want it, you will win
On your way you will see that life is more than fantasy
Take my hand, follow me
Oh, you got a brand-new friend for your life
You can win if you want
If you want it you will win
Oh Come on
Take your chance for a brand-new wild romance.
Take my hand for the night and your feelings will be right
Hold me tight.
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: You Can Win If You Want (3:50)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Oh darkness finds you're on your own
Endless highways keep on rollin' on.
You are miles and miles from your home
But you never want to phone your home.
A steady job and a nice young man
Your parents had your future planned.
Rings on her fingers
Paint on your toes
That's the way your story goes.
You can win if you want
If you want it you will win
On your way you will see that life is more than fantasy
Take my hand, follow me
Oh, you got a brand-new friend for your life
You can win if you want
If you want it you will win
Oh come on
Take your chance for a brand-new wild romance.
Take my hand for the night and your feelings will be right
Hold me tight.
You can win if you want
If you want it you will win
Oh, come on, take a chance for a brand new wild romance
Take my hand for the night
And your feelings will be right, hold me tight