Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Stranded In The Middle Of Nowhere (4:33)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Albatross
Show me a dream of love
Without her love I'm lost
Good love never dies
Angels never fly so high
I'm dreaming, dreaming
Coming back to me
I'm stranded in the middle of nowhere, take care
I'm stranded in a struggle of my dreams, it seemes
Baby, oh I need you more
Like roses need the rain
Come and take my hand
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Stranded In The Middle Of Nowhere (4:33)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Albatross
Harder I try, bluer I get
Don't leave me alone - I'm sad
Oh, I find my home
Right back where I started from
I'm dreaming, dreaming
Coming back to me
I'm stranded in the middle of nowhere, take care
I'm stranded in a struggle of my dreams, it seemes
Baby, oh I need you more
Like roses need the rain
Come and take my hand
I'm stranded
Nobody cries, time's on my side
I don't know where but you're not theree
I'm stranded
Playing the fool, breaking the rules
Take up your hand, make me a friend
I'm stranded
Nobody cries, time's on my side
I don't know where but you're not theree
I'm stranded
Playing the fool, breaking the rules