Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Geronimo's Cadillac (3:19)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-05-04
I wanna share my dreams
Wanna share with you
On the wings of love
Like dreamers do
Touch your heart
You're the queen of broken hearts
Oh we are daytime friends
And nighttime fools
Wanna play this game
You break the rules
Tears of love are frozen tears
Geronimo's Cadillac
Is making all girls too mad
Geronimo has a heart oh it's a drag
Geronimo's Cadillac
Oh making all girls too sad
Geronimo has a heart oh it's a drag
Geronimo's Cadillac
It's tossing Oh in your head
It's tossing and turning
It's burning it makes you mad
Geronimo's Cadillac Oh baby I'll hold you back
You're tossing and turning,
It's burning, it's makes you sad
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Geronimo's Cadillac (3:19)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-05-04
I'm looking through the eyes of love
Made a fool of me can't get enough
Touch my heart Boulevard of broken dreams
Another time for love other place to be
Don't let him take your love
Your love from me
Tears of love are frozen tears
Geronimo's Cadillac
Is making all girls too mad
Geronimo has a heart oh it's a drag
Geronimo's Cadillac
Oh making all girls too sad
Geronimo has a heart oh it's a drag
Geronimo's Cadillac
It's tossing Oh in your head
It's tossing and turning
It's burning it makes you mad
Geronimo's Cadillac Oh baby I'll hold you back
You're tossing and turning,
It's burning, it's makes you sad
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Geronimo's Cadillac (3:19)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-05-04
Geronimo's Cadillac
Is making all girls too mad
Geronimo has a heart oh it's a drag