Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang Vietnam
Title: You And Me (4:03)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Love delight - deep inside
I'm sharing all my love with you
Oh, why I know I can't live without you girl ?
I can't live without you
Take me away - make my day
Every time I see your face
Oh, why I know I can't live without your love ?
That I can't live without you
There's one life to live
And one heart to give
Tell me that you need, body heat
Just turn out the lights
You and me - dreams are free
Just a woman and a man, babe
You and me - can't you see
That I'm doing what I can, babe
Babe, you and me - ecstasy
And I never want to lose you
To the end of the world
Oh, I'll stay by your side
You and me - oh, I feel
Like the moon was made for lonely
You and me - and it's real
You are the one and you're the only
You and me - memories
All the love that's never ending
To the end of the world
Oh, I'll stay by your side
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang Vietnam
Title: You And Me (4:03)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
It's getting late
And I can wait
The ocean beating in my heart
Oh, why I know I can't live without you girl ?
I can't live without you
I call your name
Again and again
I lose my soul, my self control
Oh, why I know that I can't live without your love ?
That I can't live without you
There's one life to live
And one heart to give
Tell me that you need, body heat
Just turn out the light
You and me - dreams are free
Just a woman and a man, babe
You and me - can't you see
That I'm doing what I can, babe
Babe, you and me - ecstasy
And I never want to lose you
To the end of the world
Oh, I'll stay by your side
You and me - oh, I feel
Like the moon was made for lonely
You and me - and it's real
You are the one and you're the only
You and me - memories
All the love that's never ending
To the end of the world
Oh, I'll stay by your side
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang Vietnam
Title: You And Me (4:03)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com