Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Give Me Peace On Earth (4:15)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Love is easy
Hate is wrong
Find the way, babe
Way back home
Give your heart
Love will never die
Or a little cloud will cry
Be a dreamer - be a fool
Come and break all this rules
Better late than never done
For the children
We need a home
Give me peace on earth
Give me all your love
Say, that we won't fighting
For the peace of all
Give me peace on earth
Give me all your love
For the little children
For the peace of all
Come together - turn a dream
For the children, love is all we need
All the wrongs don't make it right
For the children we will fight
Give me peace on earth
Give me all your love
Say, that we won't fighting
For the peace of all
Give me peace on earth
Give me all your love
For the little children
For the peace of all
Give me peace on earth
Give me all your love
Say, that we won't fighting
For the peace of all