Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: With A Little Love (3:35)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
They said : Oh yeah, it's a tough world
You're restless and you're young
I said : Oh girl, it's a good twirl
And your time will come, your time will come
They said : you came from the wrong side
He's a page from the end of the book
I said : You came from the right side
Took me just one look
Then you understood
With a little love
You will survive
You will get by
Do what you want
Go your own way
'Cause its your life
With a little love
You'll make a start
Yeah, why lovers break each other's heart
Do what you want
Go your own way
'Cause it's your life
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: With A Little Love (3:35)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
They said : no future forget it
You came from the wrong side of town
I said : don't listen, don't let it
Let it bring you down
Make you wear a frown
They said : Oh let him down easy
Laugh at the heart you have won
I said : that life is for living
Like the morning sun
It had just began
With a little love
You will survive
You will get by
Do what you want
Go your own way
'Cause its your life
With a little love
You'll make a start
Yeah, why lovers break each other's heart
Do what you want
Go your own way
'Cause it's your life
With a little love
You'll make a start
Yeah, why lovers break each other's heart
Do what you want
Go your own way
'Cause it's your life
With a little love
You'll make a start
Yeah, why lovers break each other's heart
Do what you want
Go your own way
'Cause it's your life