Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Diamonds Never Made A Lady (4:03)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Oh my heart is crying in the night for you
Oh, my God, oh don't you feel like a fool
You're fooling yourself with a millionaire
You think it's love but he don't care
And one of these days
You're gonna be surprised
Diamonds never made a lady, lover or a friend
I know it
Diamonds never made a lady, all your dreams will end
Your Californian nights
Warm body held you tight
Was just a dream
But all the diamond lights
Can't give you peacefull lives or sweet dreams
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Diamonds Never Made A Lady (4:03)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Oh my God, you really think you have it made
Your heart is won, with first class expenses paid
You drink champaign, eat caviar
A colour TV in the back of your car
But one of these days
You're gonna be surpised
Diamonds never made a lady, lover or a friend
I know it
Diamonds never made a lady, all your dreams will end
Your Californian nights
Warm body held you tight
Was just a dream
But all the diamond lights
Can't give you peacefull lives or sweet dreams
Your Californian nights
Warm body held you tight
Was just a dream
But all the diamond lights
Can't give you peacefull lives or sweet dreams
Your Californian nights
Warm body held you tight
Was just a dream