Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Let's Talk About Love (3:56)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Let me rock you, let me roll you
Take my hand
I will take you to a new start
Calling the promised land
Let me love you, let me hold you
With all my heart
Trust me baby, like I trust you
I did it from the start
And each and every day
I'm gonna always say
Let's talk about love, love, love, love
That's all I'm dreaming of
Let's talk about love
It's up to you
To make your dreams come true
Look in my eyes, there's a way
Don't throw your dreams away
You'll never lose
Keep love alive
Babe, then our love survive
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Let's Talk About Love (3:56)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Let me rock you, let me roll you
I'll be close to you
We can have a one way trip to paradise for two
There's so much
I can give you
I'll give all my heart
We can always be together
And never break apart
And each and every day I'm gonna always say
Let's talk about love, love, love, love
That's all I'm dreaming of
Let's talk about love
It's up to you
To make your dreams come true
Look in my eyes, there's a way
Don't throw your dreams away
You'll never lose
Keep love alive
Babe, then our love survive
Let's talk about love, love, love, love
That's all I'm dreaming of
Let's talk about love
It's up to you
To make your dreams come true
Let's talk about love, love, love, love