Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Jet Airliner (4:23)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
The times were hard and I was running
I could feel my chance was coming
Another time, another place
A pillow filled with frozen tears
See the gates, a distant fire
Shows the way, to my desire
Laying down my heart for you
'Cause I'm lonely, feelin' blue
I know that I'll never die on love
But I'll never get enough
Oh, I got no time to lose
On my avenue to a jet airliner
Avenue to my broken dreams
My avenue to a jet airliner
Like an old old movie-scene
Brings me back to the dreams I loved
Good guys only win in movies
But this time babe I'll get enough
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Jet Airliner (4:23)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03
Love can breed misunderstanding
But my heart will soon be landing
Another love on golden wings
Oh, I'll buy you diamond rings
Waitin' for a lonely rainbow
Magic wave where will I go
Breaking down my heart to you
'Cause I'm lonely, feelin' blue
I know that I'll never die on love
But I'll never get enough
Oh, I got no time to lose
On my avenue to a jet airliner
Avenue to my broken dreams
My avenue to a jet airliner
Like an old old movie-scene
Brings me back to the dreams I loved
Good guys only win in movies
But this time babe I'll get enough
Artist: Modern Talking
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Jet Airliner (4:23)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-04-03