Artist: N'sync
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Thinking Of You (4:02)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-05-08
Lying in your arms
So close together
Didn't know just what i had
Now i toss and turn
Cause i'm without you
How i'm missingyou so bad
Where was my head
Where was my heart
Now i cry alone in the dark
I lay awake
I drive myself crazy
Drive myself crazy
Thingking of you
Made a mistake
When i let you go baby
I drive myself crazy
Wanting you the way that i do
I was such a fool
I couldn't see it
Just how good you were tome
You confessed your love
Undying devotion
I confessed my need to be free
And now i'n left
With all this pain
I've only got
Mysilf to blame
I lay awake
I drive myself crazy
Drive myself crazy
Thingking of you
Made a mistake
When i let you go baby
I drive myself crazy
Wanting you the way that i do
Why didn't i know it
(how much i loved you baby)
Why couldn't i show it
(if i had only told you )
When i had the chance
Oh i hand the chance
Artist: N'sync
Album: Tuan Anh Computer 258 T.N.Han TP BacGiang, Vietnam
Title: Thinking Of You (4:02)
By: nguyentuan2005@gmail.com
Date: 2010-05-08
I lay awake
I drive myself crazy
Drive myself crazy
Thingking of you
Made a mistake
When i let you go baby
I drive myself crazy
Wanting you the way that i do
I lay awake
I drive myself crazy
Drive myself crazy
Thingking of you
Made a mistake
When i let you go baby
I drive myself crazy
Wanting you the way that i do